Contact

ektiegs@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/elice-t-323440151 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Research

Nursing

Hospitals

Certifications

American Nurses Credentialing Center

Advanced Trauma Life Support State of Minnesota Public Health Nurse

Emergency Nurse Association

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International Honor Society of Nursing Allina Key Contributor

Elice Tiegs

A Dedicated, Results Oriented Nurse Practitioner Seeking Opportunities In The Medical, Research or Pharmaceutical Fields Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

Summary

Passion for networking with like-minded individuals who have a strong interest in the healthcare field. Promoting diversity in the workplace to make sure the opportunity exists for all nationalities.

A hardworking, highly driven, motivated and enthusiastic self-starter seeks advancement to effectively utilize my strong knowledge in the medical and pharmaceutical fields. Interests include medical research, biotechnology, medical devices and pharmaceuticals.

Open for relocation with a willingness to travel up to 80% of the time.

Experience

Emergency Physicians, PA (EPPA) Nurse Practitioner 2015 - January 2019 (4 years)

Emergency Care Consultants
Nurse Practitioner
December 2008 - August 2015 (6 years 9 months)
Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

St. Catherine University
Adjunct Faculty
2013 - 2014 (1 year)
Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

University of Minnesota-Twin Cities Adjunct Faculty 2012 - 2014 (2 years) Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

St. Francis Regional Medical Center - Urgent Care

Nurse Practitioner 2011 - 2013 (2 years) Shakopee, Minnesota

Park Nicollet Methodist Hosptial Nurse 1997 - 2008 (11 years) St. Louis Park, Minnesota

University of Minnesota-Twin Cities Research Assistant 2005 - 2006 (1 year) Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

Education

University of Minnesota-Twin Cities

University of Minnesota-Twin Cities
Masters of Science in Nursing (MSN), Family Nurse Practitioner